thinkcerca.com 2015-03-27

# ThinkCERCA | Think Critical. Think Collaboration.

This Privacy Policy describes our privacy practices for Thinkcerca.com Inc, our web-based platform and related sites and services (collectively, the “Service”). Our Service allows users create and use lessons for crtitical thinking. The Service provides Web-based tools to easily create lessons, which consist of a content from third party sources and ThinkCERCA.com Inc. We provide the Service from our Web site and from mobile applications, mobile sites or other Internet points of presence that we may make available from time to time (collectively, our “Site”). By using or accessing our Service and Site, you agree to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use. If you have questions about our privacy practices, please contact us at [support@thinkcerca.com](mailto:support@thinkcerca.com)

**1\. SCOPE OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY.**

This Privacy Policy covers our collection and use of information when you use our Service and Site. It does not cover third party Web sites or applications to which we provide links from our Service.

**2\. INFORMATION WE COLLECT FROM USERS.**

In order to use the Service, users must submit their name and email to the Service. This is the only personally identifiable information we collect from users (including students). The Service provides users with one place to organize and present their knowledge and content. Students may sign up either by going to the site or by a teacher adding them to a class. We use the names and email address of students only to provide the Service, and do not disclose them to anyone other than a student’s own teacher and school administrator except under the circumstances described in Section 5 below.

**3\. INFORMATION WE COLLECT FROM USERS.**

  * Personal Information You Provide at Registration. If you register for an account on our Service, we ask for your name and email address.
  * Information We Collect When You Use Our Service. We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with our Service. We keep track of your “clicks” and pages you view on our Site. We use “cookies” and obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses the Site, such as the Internet Protocol (IP) address of your computer, information about your browser software and operating system, and the date and time you access our site. “Cookies” are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and provide certain features on our Site. The “Help” feature in most Web browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable some cookies altogether. Keep in mind that disabling cookies may result in some features of the Service not working properly.

**4\. HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT.**

  * To Provide, Manage and Improve the Services and Sites. We use the personal information we collect from users to make the Service, the Sites and its features available, and to improve and add features to the Service and the Sites. We may also use this information to customize certain Service and the Sites features for teachers.
  * To Contact Users and Respond to Emails. We may also use contact information to provide teachers with announcements related to our services. If you email us, we may use your email addresses to respond.

**5\. HOW WE SHARE PERSONAL INFORMATION.**

We do not share any personal information submitted to the Service by users with any third parties, except under the following limited circumstances: 

  * Third Party Service Providers. We rely on some third party service providers to assist us in operating the Service. For example, we may use third parties to host our Site or send messages. We provide personal information to these third party service providers in order to help us operates the Service, but we put in place contractual and/or technical protections that prohibit them from using that information, or it to any third party, except as necessary in operating the Service.
  * Business Transfers. If we (or our assets) are acquired by another company, personal information you submit to the Service would likely be among the assets transferred to the acquirer. In the event of such an acquisition, the Privacy Policy in force at the time would continue to apply your information.
  * To Protect Us and Others from Liability or Harm. We release message content and personal information if we believe we must do so to comply with the law, to enforce our Terms of Use, or to protect the safety and rights of us or our users. This does not include selling, renting, sharing or disclosing your information or content for commercial purposes.
  * With Your Consent. We may also share your personal information or content with third parties if you give us your consent to do so.

**6\. HOW TO VIEW AND EDIT YOUR INFORMATION; ACCOUNT DELETION**

  * Profile Information. You can view and modify your account information on the Service at any time.
  * Account Deletion. If you wish to delete your account or contact information from the Service, please email us at [support@thinkcerca.com](mailto:support@thinkcerca.com) requesting deletion.

**7\. MESSAGE CONTENT.**

We do not monitor, review or exercise any control over the resources used when using the Service (though we reserve the right to block resources that we reasonably believe may subject us or our users to liability). Accordingly, personal information included in the content of resources used on the Service is not governed by this Privacy Policy. We encourage you to avoid including personally identifiable information about yourself or others in resources and lessons that will be shared or made public, and we encourage teachers to talk with their students about not including sensitive personal information in any resource or lesson used on the Service.

**8\. SECURITY.**

We take precautions to maintain the security and integrity of personal information you submit to the Service, including storage of your profile and personal information on a secure server behind a firewall.

**9\. MODIFICATIONS TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY.**

We may modify this Privacy Policy at any time. If you maintain an account for the Service, we will notify you, at the email address you provide to us when you register for an account, of any material modifications to this Privacy Statement.

**10\. HOW TO CONTACT US.**

If you have any questions about our privacy practices, please contact us at [support@thinkcerca.com](mailto:support@thinkcerca.com) or call us at 708-79-CERCA.
